peachtree.com 2015-12-15

# Legal | Sage North America | U.S.

## Copyright and trademark

All materials available through this website and other websites owned or provided by Sage or any of its affiliated entities (collectively “Sage”), including any products, services, and web content including but not limited to software, images, text, and various downloads (“Materials”) are owned by Sage and/or by Sage vendors, who have given permission to use the Materials.

Materials are protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws and all rights in the Materials are reserved by Sage or their respective owners. You may view, copy, and print pages from the website for personal use only. You may not otherwise use, reproduce, download, modify, store, post, broadcast, transmit, sell, or make available to any party any part of the content from the website without the prior written approval of Sage. 

#### Copyright notice

© 2015 Sage Software, Inc. All Rights Reserved.

#### Trademark notice

Sage owns many valuable trademarks worldwide that represent Sage as well as its products and services. Most Sage trademarks are registered in the U.S. and in other countries, typically in the name of Sage. Sage does not use the trademark legends.

All references to Sage and Sage products and services must be accurate and never misleading in any way. Sage trademarks may only be used to refer to Sage and Sage products and services, and may not be combined with any other company names, product names, services names, or as part of any domain names. Sage logos are reserved for exclusive use by Sage, its licensees, and partners under written contract with Sage. No other uses of the Sage logos are permitted.

The following products, services, and taglines listed herein as well as related logos are registered trademarks or trademarks of Sage and/or its affiliates in the US and/or other countries. This list is provided here for reference only and may not be complete or current and will change from time to time. 

Sage; Sage Software; Sage logos; Sage Connected Services; Sage Cloud Services; SData; Sage E-Marketing; Sage Information System; Sage Summit; Sage View, Sage Advisor; Sage Communicator; Sage Harmonizer; Sage Messaging; Sage Migrator; Sage Project Lifecycle Management; Get The Insights Behind Your Numbers; Helping Those Who Do Good Things Do Them Even Better; It Turns Time Into Money; Smartimer; Simply Accounting; Abra; Accpac; Accuracy, Control, Results; Business Care; BusinessVision; BusinessWorks; DacEasy; FirstStep; MAS; MAS 90; MAS 200; MAS 500; Master Builder; Payment Boss; Peachtree; ProAlert; Return on Employee Investment; ROEI; Your Business in Mind Your Relationships. Your Information. Your CRM; Telemagic; Timeslips; TSRemote; TSTimer; ULTIA; Sage DataSage; Sage Transaction Services

Sage One; Sage One Accounting; Sage One Accounting Standard; Sage One Invoicing; Sage One Accountant Edition; Sage One Accountant Pack; Sage One Connect; Sage Accountants Network; SAN; Sage Accountant Solutions; Leadership Education for Accounting Professionals (LEAP) 

Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate; Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate Project Management; Sage 300 Trade Specialty; Sage 100 Contractor; Sage Construction Anywhere; Sage Estimating; Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate Office Connector; Sage 300 Office Connector Import; Sage 300 Office Connector Financials; Sage 300 Office Connector Query; Sage 300 Office Connector Write; Sage Paperless Construction; Sage Service Operations; Sage Service Operations for Technicians; Sage Service Operations for Customers; Sage Estimating eTakeoff Dimension; Sage Estimating eTakeoff Bridge; Sage Estimating Cut & Fill; Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate Document Management; Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate MyAssistant; Sage 300 Construction and Real Estate MyCommunicator for Outlook; PlanSwift for Sage; Sage Estimating ePlan Takeoff Integrator; Sage Bid Management; Sage Construction Project Management; Sage Estimating Advanced Assembly Databases; Sage Estimating Industry Databases; Sage Estimating Knowledgebases; Sage Estimating RSMeans Databases; Sage Construction and Real Estate Forms; Sage Academy; Sage Anytime Learning; Sage Realtime Learning; Sage Replay Learning.

Sage 100; Sage 100 Standard ERP; Sage 100 Advanced ERP; Sage 100 Premium ERP; Sage 100 Online; Sage 300; Sage 300 Standard ERP; Sage 300 Advanced ERP; Sage 300 Premium ERP; Sage 300 Online; Sage 300 Online; Sage 500 ERP; Sage MAS 90; Sage MAS 200; Sage MAS 500.

Sage Payment Solutions, Sage Exchange; Sage Merchant Account; Sage ACH Account; Sage Virtual Terminal; Sage Mobile Payments; Sage Virtual Check (ACH); Sage Point of Sale Check Conversion; Sage Check 21; Sage Gift Card; Sage Loyalty Card; Sage Small Business Loan; Sage International Payments; Sage Account Updater; Sage Chargeback Assistance Program; Sage Terminal Replacement Program.

Sage Payroll Solutions, Sage Payroll Services; Sage Payroll Full Service, Sage Payroll Essentials; Sage Time; Sage BusinessVision; Sage BusinessWorks; Sage DacEasy; Sage Fixed Assets; Sage HRMS; Sage Timeslips; EasyChoice; Encore; Paychoice; Paychoice Connection; PeopleChoice HR; Payroll in a Flash; Online Employer; Paychoice Online; Sage Active Planner; Sage Source

SageCRM; SageCRM.com; Sage X3 

#### Third-party trademarks

Business Objects® and the Business Objects logo, BusinessObjects®, and Crystal Reports® are trademarks or registered trademarks of Business Objects Software Ltd. in the United States and in other countries. Business Objects is an SAP company.

UPS®, the UPS brandmark and the Color Brown are trademarks of United Parcel Service of America Inc. Citrix®, GoToMyPC®, GoToMeeting®, GoToWebinar®, GoToAssistExpress®, and Access Your PC from Anywhere® are trademarks of Citrix Systems, Inc. and/or one or more of its affiliates and may be registered in the United States Patent and Trademark Office and in other countries.

Microsoft ®SQL Server®, Windows Vista® and the Windows logo are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or in other countries. The names of all other products and services are property of their respective owners.

#### Questions

For questions regarding Sage copyrights or trademarks, please contact the Sage North America Legal Department:

Legal Department   
Sage   
1715 N. Brown Road   
Lawrenceville, GA 30043 

## Sage North America Privacy Policy (Excluding Sage Payroll)

Updated: April 24, 2015

Sage is committed to the security and privacy of our customer’s data. This Privacy Policy explains our commitment to safeguarding our customers’ data and serves as our agreement with our customers and other parties about our data handling practices. This policy lists the types of data we collect, explains how we use and protect that data, and discloses our key procedures surrounding privacy.

Sage is part of a group of affiliated companies collectively referred to as the "Sage Companies" with each such affiliated company being directly or indirectly wholly owned by The Sage Group plc (The Sage Group). This Privacy Policy applies only to Sage in North America. All other Sage Companies are governed by their own respective policies.

This privacy policy is a binding agreement between you and Sage. By accessing any of our product or company websites (the “Sites”), you signify that you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version here, and the new version will become effective immediately.

The privacy of our customers and affiliates is important to us. Therefore: 

  * We do not sell or rent personally identifiable information
  * We do not spam, and our policies forbid use of our Services for spam

#### Public forums

Please remember that any information (including personal and business information) that you submit, post or otherwise reveal in a public forum (such as a bulletin board, chat room, blog or product discussion forum) is not subject to this Privacy Policy, will be seen by third parties not related to us and may be used by them or us to contact you for any purpose.

#### Statement regarding children 

Sage's products and services are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. As such, the Sites are not directed at children under the age of 13 nor do we knowingly collect or maintain information from children under the age of 13 on the Sites.

#### Job seekers

We will use the personal information you submit in our online job application to fill the specific position you apply for. After this position is filled, we will retain the information submitted for the time required by applicable law or in accordance with our standard practice, whichever is longer.

We will not release information submitted in online job applications to third parties except to appropriate governmental entities and/or our service providers as necessary in connection with recruiting, employment, corporate governance, acquisitions, and legal or regulatory requirements. We require that our service providers keep your personal information confidential as well. In addition, to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard the information we collect online. You may submit requests or concerns about this policy or use of your personal information by email to [RecruitingNA@sage.com](mailto:RecruitingNA@sage.com).

#### Business information collection and use by Sage

We collect the Business Information necessary to enable us to respond to your requests for our products and services and to send you information regarding our products and services from time to time. Since most of the users of our products and Sites are doing so in their capacity as employees or companies, most Business Information we collect will be in that capacity (rather than information about you individually, such as your personal tastes, etc.). For these purposes, we have defined "Business Information" as any information that identifies or may identify a company or an individual contact at a company or that allows others to contact a company or an individual contact at a company. When you visit the Sites, you may be asked to submit information such as email address, company name, address, phone number, your product version, and/or areas of interest. We may also ask you where you heard about our company or products, or for other information that will help us understand more about your needs or help us process your requests for information. In addition, we collect credit card and related payment information when you order products, services, or support plans online. Our information collection and use practices are described in more detail below:

  * Product registration. You may be asked, on behalf of your company, to complete registration/activation form(s) on the Sites or from within the products, with contact information for use by us in accordance with this policy. Registration or activation information may include the name of your company, contact information, product information, customer ID, network and operating system, and other relevant information.
  * Customer profile. We also collect Business Information when you create a customer profile or Passport account on some of the Sites, which is required in order to access certain areas of the Sites, purchase support plans and products, to obtain software downloads and certain online support services, and to request information from us about our products and services. This information includes company name and contact information and other information about your company (for example, size, revenue, and number of employees), the products you may have licensed, and other non-Sage products you may currently use. We use this information in accordance with this policy to identify you, process your requests, and administer your Sage account(s).
  * Support. We offer certain limited online support services at the Sites. If you access online support on any of the Sites, you may be asked for information such as customer ID, product name, product version, and other information to help us determine what the technical issues are and how best to help you resolve them. In addition, certain products allow you to submit support-related questions directly from the product. If you access online support services from a product, information about your network, operating system, printer, data and program path, product type, version, customer ID, the product's technical support information sheet, product serial number, and other similar information will be automatically pre-populated for submission to our customer support representatives to assist them in answering your questions.
  * Newsletters. When you subscribe or sign up to receive newsletters published or offered via the Sites, we will ask you for information necessary to enable us to process your request and to send you information regarding our products and services.
  * Cookies. We also use Cookies to enhance the user experience, deliver personalized content, and collect information about the use of the Sites. "Cookies" are small computer files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to statistically monitor how many people are using the Sites and for what purposes, how often someone visits the Sites, and the length of their stay. This information helps us dynamically generate advertising and information specifically designed for your interests. We also use Cookies to prevent you from having to re-enter your identification and password information each time you visit our Sites. Cookies are not designed to retrieve personal or business data from your hard drive, your email, or any other personal information. Most browsers are initially set to accept Cookies, but users can change the setting to refuse Cookies or to be alerted when Cookies are being sent. Although refusal of Cookies will not interfere with the ability to interact with most of the Sites, you will need to accept Cookies in order to access information and use certain functions. For example, Cookies are required to be accepted for access to our web-based services or desktop products with online features. The Cookies are renewed each time a user logs on to one of the Sites that uses Cookies. 

Although the majority of the online advertisements on the Sites are displayed by Sage, we also from time to time allow third-party vendors, such as Google, to display advertisements on the Sites. These third-party vendors may assign a different cookie to you. These cookies may be used to select which ads you see on the Sites and determine the effectiveness of this advertising. You may choose to decline cookies from third-party ad servers, which we do not control. If you would like to opt out from receiving these third-party targeted advertisements, you can read the instructions.

  * Product-related information collection. We collect certain additional information in connection with your use of our services or desktop products with online features. For instance: 
    * Product updates. Some products provide you with the ability to download and register product and/or tax updates as they become available. During the download and registration process, we collect Business Information, including customer ID number and product version, type, and serial number, in order to authorize your access and provide you with the appropriate update, and to update our records as to the product and products updates you have downloaded or installed.
    * Account set-up and access. Upon subscribing to our services, we collect Business Information which may include information such as product serial number, customer ID, and your customer profile information, in order to identify you and authorize your access and use of the services and provide you with your relevant account information. Certain products provide you with the ability to access your account in order to obtain information such as your support plan status, service subscriptions, registrations, and order history. 
    * Online product/account application. Certain products and services are subject to an application and enrollment process, which may be completed on paper or online. Information requested may include federal ID numbers, bank account, payroll, credit card, and contact information. This information is used to process your enrollment request and, if approved, to set up and administer your account.
    * Web-based services. In connection with certain of our web-based services we collect certain additional information, including IP address, browser, connection speed, domain, referring URL, and other environment-related information to enable us to provide a secure environment for the use of the services, to pre-populate forms, and calculate aggregate statistical information about the customers using these services.
    * Sage products and services. In addition to the uses set forth above, we may use your Business Information to: 1) inform you of product upgrades and updates and subscription renewals; 2) inform you of tax, regulatory, and other compliance issues with your software product or service; 3) notify you of products and services that we think may be of interest to you; 4) offer you discounts or other promotions with respect to Sage products and services that we think may interest you; and 5) contact you for survey purposes to determine how we can better service you or provide better products to meet your needs. 
    * Other Sage company products and services. Your Business Information may be provided to one or more other Sage Companies to enable them to market products and services to you. In that case, the use of your Business Information would be governed by that Sage Company's privacy policy.
    *     * Third-party products. We may also use your Business Information to inform you of special discounts or offers from other companies we have carefully selected and whose products and services may be of interest to you.

#### Disclosure of your business information 

From time to time, we may be required to release Business Information: 1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order; 2) to enforce or apply the terms of any of our service or license agreements; or 3) in special cases, such as protecting the rights, property, or safety of Sage, our customers, or others. We may also provide Business Information to government agencies and to our vendors, suppliers, authorized resellers, and other business, development, and industry partners ("Partners") to enable them to: 1) provide us with products and services to better operate and maintain the Sites; 2) provide you with a product or service requested by you; or 3) enable them to market products or services to you. We also may provide information about you that does not allow you to be identified to, or contacted by, third parties ("Aggregate Information"). For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of the Sites and the activities they conduct while on the Sites. Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge for this Aggregate Information. We may also use this Aggregate Information as part of products or services that we provide to third parties and to improve our products, services, and the Sites.

  * Partner and government services. We may engage Partners to perform functions on our behalf, which may include assisting us in processing your Business Information. Certain Partners and government agencies may collect Business Information (such as business name, address, email address, credit card information, and customer ID) directly from you and use of that information and other information provided by you to third parties is not governed by this policy even though those Partners and government agencies may share such information with us. 
  * Services and product data. Business Information collected by us as set forth above does not include your company's data entered in the course of operating our products ("Product Data") or data provided by you while using our services ("Services Data"). We will not access your Product Data or Services Data except in the following limited circumstances: (1) to provide you with technical support, solely at your request and with your permission; (2) on a limited-access basis to install updates, produce regular backups, or restore data from backups at your request; (3) where the inherent purpose of the product or service requires us to provide the Product Data or Services Data to a third party on your behalf (for example where we makes tax filings on your behalf or initiate bank transfers on your behalf) and, (4) unless you opt-out, to utilize Aggregate Information derived from Product Data and Services Data to help us improve our products and services and in developing additional offerings. We will not provide your Product Data or Services Data to any third party or permit any third party to access your Product Data or Services Data, except by your permission or to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order. In addition, if at any time you decide to discontinue your use of the applicable service, your Services Data will be destroyed and removed from all servers according to terms set forth in your Service Agreement. 
  * Business transfers. In the event that all or a portion of Sage or any other Sage Company (or the assets of one of those entities), is bought or sold, Business Information will likely be included among the transferred business assets, but such information remains subject to this Privacy Policy or a Privacy Policy substantially similar to this privacy Policy.

#### How Sage protects your privacy internally

We want your Business Information to remain as secure as reasonably possible. We combine industry-standard technical safeguards with a code of conduct for those employees who are permitted to access our customers' Business Information. When you purchase a product or service online, we use SSL encryption to encrypt your credit card information before it is sent to us in order to ensure the integrity and privacy of the credit card information that you provide to us via the Internet.

Many of our web-based services are hosted on servers that are co-located at a third-party facility with whom we have a contract providing for security measures. For example, hosted Services Data is submitted via SSL encryption and stored on a server equipped with industry standard firewalls.

Hosted data may include personally identifiable information and other information that belongs to our customers' own customers, website visitors, or other users. We will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the service or license agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records of Customer Data may be viewed or accessed by authorized Sage employees, agents or independent contractors only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the service or license agreement, or as may be required by law. Sage policy requires that both employees and consultants execute a confidentiality agreement before working for and with Sage. Those employees that violate our Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

Despite these security measures, we do not represent or warrant that Business Information will be protected against loss, misuse, attacks, or alteration by third parties. Customers are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their usernames and passwords.

#### Your privacy choices

Occasionally, a Sage business unit may send you communications to provide you with information or promotions relating to products and services that may be of interest to you, including notification of important product issues and updates. You may opt out of receiving these communications as indicated below. However, please note that any election not to receive future communications applies only to promotional messages of the particular Sage business unit and you may receive promotional messages from other Sage business units until you make an opt out request with that business unit as indicated below. Additionally, we may still send you relationship or transactional messages in order to notify you of important product issues and updates, such as tax and other compliance-related matters, for the renewal of existing subscription services, to resolve specific questions or requests made by you via phone, fax, email, or the Web and in response to any activity completed on any of the Sites, including but not limited to, registration, ordering, downloads, and requests for information.

  * Sage email promotions. Each email we send will contain instructions on how to unsubscribe in the event that you do not wish to receive future promotional emails from the Sage business unit that sent you the email promotion. If you choose to opt out of receiving promotional email communications from any Sage business unit, we may still periodically communicate with you via mail and telephone. Please allow 10 business days to be removed from the promotional email list of a Sage business unit.
  * Third-party email promotions. If you access and/or use any of the other Sage Companies' services or our Partner's services from a link on the Sites, a Sage/Partner co-branded site or by any other means, any information you reveal in connection with such service is submitted to that other Sage Company or to our Partner and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should consult the privacy policy of any other Sage Company, Partner, or third-party site with respect to its treatment of any information that you may reveal in connection with such service.

##### Correcting or updating your business information and contacting Sage

You can always update the Business Information that you have provided to us and/or change your preferences with respect to marketing contacts from us by contacting the Sage business unit to which you provided your preferences. Please note that it may take up to 4 weeks to be removed from the Sage business unit’s mail lists and 10 days to be removed from email and phone lists.

#### Linked sites

The Sites may contain links to third-party websites and resources (collectively, "Linked Sites"). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by us of the content on such Linked Sites. We make no representations or warranties regarding the correctness, accuracy, performance, or quality of any content, software, service, or application found at any Linked Site. We are not responsible for the availability of the Linked Sites or the content or activities of such sites. If you decide to access any Linked Site, you do so at your own risk. Your use of any Linked Site is subject to the policies, terms of use, and privacy policies of such Linked Site, if any.

#### Consent to transfer

Users located outside the United States who submit Business Information to us via the Sites should be aware that the information they submit will be transferred to our servers located in the United States. Your submission of Business Information to us constitutes your consent to this transfer. Although we will collect and use your Business Information only as stated in this Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the United States may not be as stringent as those in some users' home jurisdictions.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the then current policy to the Sites. Your use of the Sites constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy.

#### Questions

Email [privacy.na@sage.com](mailto:Privacy.na@sage.com).

## Sage Payroll Privacy Policy

Please read this notice carefully to understand how we collect, use, protect and otherwise handle your personal information. 

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or use our services. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. As a result of our relationship with your employer, we may capture other information, including bank account number(s) and social security number.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs and preferences)
  * To process payroll and related transactions
  * To send periodic emails
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering our services.

#### How do we protect your information?

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We only offer our services through the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and stored in our encrypted Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Your private information will be kept on file in order to provide payroll and related services.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in providing our services, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our OnlineEmployer.com website at http://www.sage.com/us/legal/online.

#### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 4/8/2015.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Sage Payroll   
305 Fellowship Rd, Suite 300  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
856-231-4667 

## Corporate compliance and employment compliance

Sage complies with applicable North American and U.K. business conduct laws and regulations.

#### Antibribery and corruption

On July 1, 2011, the United Kingdom Antibribery Act 2010 became effective in the U.K. This law requires all U.K. businesses and their subsidiaries to comply with stringent antibribery legislation. The Antibribery Act introduces rigorous antibribery guidelines with serious consequences for both businesses and individuals who fail to comply. The Antibribery Act dictates that regardless of the country in which bribery takes place, if that bribery is committed for or on behalf of a U.K. business, then the Antibribery Act will apply.

Because The Sage Group plc is a U.K.-headquartered business, its subsidiaries, including our business here in North America, must comply with the U.K. Antibribery Act. To ensure that we comply, we have introduced a new Antibribery and Corruption Policy. The key principles of the Sage North America Antibribery and Corruption Policy are set out below.

  * Sage and its employees do not and will not offer, promise, or give bribes or request, agree to receive, or accept bribes in any form (a bribe can be an offer of money but also any other financial or nonfinancial advantage or reward).
  * Anyone acting for or on behalf of Sage (including some third parties or business partners we work with) must also refrain from engaging in any of the activities set out above.
  * If anyone at Sage is concerned that this type of activity may be happening in the business, he or she can report it immediately and confidentially and be confident that action will be taken.
  * The new policy does not prevent reasonable and proportionate gifts, hospitality, and entertainment, but where those gifts, hospitality, and entertainment are unreasonable, disproportionate, or given in inappropriate circumstances (for example, when a Sage employee is considering whether to award a contract to someone) then they may constitute bribes and should not be offered or accepted. Common sense should always prevail.

Sage takes these principles very seriously and will continue to monitor and review any bribery and corruption risks which the business might face.

Sage is an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. We participate in E-Verify.

  * E-Verify participation poster ([English](http://www.uscis.gov/USCIS/Controlled%20Vocabulary/Native%20Documents/E-Verify/E-Verify_Poster_V08-08_Standard_English.pdf) / [Spanish](http://www.uscis.gov/USCIS/E-Verify/EverifyPosterSpanish1.pdf))
  * Right to work poster ([English](http://www.uscis.gov/USCIS/Verification/E-Verify/E-Verify_Native_Documents/Right_to_Work_Poster_English.pdf) / [Spanish](http://www.uscis.gov/USCIS/Verification/E-Verify/E-Verify_Native_Documents/Right_to_Work_Poster_Spanish.pdf))

#### Job seekers

We will use the personal information you submit in our online job application to fill the specific position you apply for. After this position is filled, we will retain the information submitted for the time required by applicable law or in accordance with our standard practice, whichever is longer.

We will not release information submitted in online job applications to third parties except to appropriate governmental entities and/or our service providers as necessary in connection with recruiting, employment, corporate governance, acquisitions, and legal or regulatory requirements. We require that our service providers keep your personal information confidential as well. In addition, to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard the information we collect online. You may submit requests or concerns about this policy or use of your personal information by email to [RecruitingNA@sage.com](mailto:RecruitingNA@sage.com). 

## End-user license agreement

Get more information about our license agreements.

Go
